<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-05-19T12:26:07+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Axolotl Tank</title><subtitle>A place for people like tech</subtitle><author><name>AxolotlAgatsuma</name></author><entry><title type="html">World of Engineers, a new modpack.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/worldofengineers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="World of Engineers, a new modpack." /><published>2024-05-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/worldofengineers</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/worldofengineers.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hiya! As always this is axolotl, in this post I’ll tell you some stuff about my newest project.
I am very happy and proud to show you guy our newest project, a Minecraft modpack actually, World of Engineers. To be honest the modpack is made by my friend, elroNd. He is fond of linux and modpacks. Anyways I am not going to introduce him to you guys, this post is about the modpack. 
If you know something about the latest Minecraft mods, you probably heard the name “Create” it’s a very popular tech mod pretty much meta of the tech mods. This modpack is based around it too because one, it is really fun to play with Create contraptions two, it would be a sin not to do so xD. Moreover unlike the other old tech mods you don’t need a wiki open in the background to know things, Create has it’s own wiki known as “Ponder”. When you enter ponder it shows you some examples and the things that this block/item can do. 
Other than that modpack has Tectonic, a worldgen mod that is capable of really cool terrain generation. Blue Skies for 2 new dimensions The Aether and The Twilight Forest to be exact, Tetra so you can make your own tools. “Integrated Dungeons and Structures” and “Dungeons and Taverns” to have exciting structures in your world, some non-copyrighted music with Medieval Music. Immersive Aircraft, Eureka Ships and Small Ships so we can make our own transportation vehicles. Serene Seasons because it adds the four seasons to the game and Farmer’s Delight to expand farming in the game. A lot of Vanilla+ features as Quark, Supplementaries, Amendments, Handcrafted and more. Right now we are working on a quest system, if you want to help slide into my DMs. Oh and I almost forgot here is the CurseForge page and website of the Modpack <a href="https://www.curseforge.com/minecraft/modpacks/world-of-engineers">CurseForge</a> <a href="https://axolotlagatsuma.github.io/world-of-engineers">Website</a> By the way I developed the website. :D</p>]]></content><author><name>Axolotl Agatsuma</name></author><category term="gaming" /><category term="gaming" /><category term="mods" /><category term="minecraft" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another new project...]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Where am I in my life?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/whereinlife.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where am I in my life?" /><published>2024-04-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/whereinlife</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/whereinlife.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hiya!
This is axolotl, in this post I’ll tell you some stuff about my life.
If you read my other post <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Who am I</code> you’ll know that I am Turkish. In Turkey we got a national day called “April 23rd, National Sovereignty and Children’s Day” you can say what’s the fuzz about it? The reason why we got a national day called “Children’s Day” is because our first president and founder of Turkey “Atatürk” was opening the Turkish National Assembly… Little info, it wasn’t called Turkish when Atatürk were opening it now let’s continue. …he heard there weren’t a national day that is dedicated to childrens, the future of the Earth. He quickly dedicated the opening day of the Turkish National Assembly to childrens and obviously sovereignty because we opened our parliment/assembly. By the way Atatürk dedicated the day to all childrens not only Turkish childrens. Because of that in that day all schools and goverment buildings are in holiday or have special programs and shows. I would say more stuff but I gotta leave so see you guys later! You guys can dm me from GitHub.</p>]]></content><author><name>Axolotl Agatsuma</name></author><category term="about_me" /><category term="author" /><category term="irl" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is like a diary.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Who am I?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/whoami.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Who am I?" /><published>2024-03-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/whoami</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/whoami.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hiya!
This is axolotl, your friendly tech guy. I am a [REDACTED] year old Turkish selftaught programmer and student. Right now I am working on a stupid exam paper that’ll determine my whole life.</p>]]></content><author><name>Axolotl Agatsuma</name></author><category term="about_me" /><category term="author" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who is AxolotlAgatsuma, the guy behind this website?]]></summary></entry></feed>